const Qdata = [
{question:"what is this?",
options:["A","B","C","D"],
correct:"A",
Qid:"123"},
{question:"why is this?",
options:["1","B","3","D"],
correct:"A",
Qid:"124"},
{question:"hhh is this?",
options:["1","2","3","D"],
correct:"D",
Qid:"126"},
{question:"hhhFDF is this?",
options:["1","Q","3","D"],
correct:"Q",
Qid:"166"},
{question:"hhhFDF is this?",
options:["1","N","3","D"],
correct:"N",
Qid:"156"},
{question:"hhhFDF is this?",
options:["1","L","3","D"],
correct:"L",
Qid:"146"},
{question:"hhhFDF is this?",
options:["1","P","J","D"],
correct:"J",
Qid:"136"},
{question:"hhhFDF is this?",
options:["1","P","R","D"],
correct:"R",
Qid:"026"},
{question:"hhhFDF is this?",
options:["1","P","F","D"],
correct:"F",
Qid:"116"},
{question:"hhhFDF is this?",
options:["1","P","4","D"],
correct:"4",
Qid:"106"}

];
export default(n=5)=>
Promise.resolve(Qdata.sort(()=>0.5-Math.random()).slice(0,n));
